[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Could The Body be planning a run for the White House?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "The", "Body", "be", "planning", "a", "run", "for", "the", "White", "House", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "You'll be the first to know, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "be", "the", "first", "to", "know", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Ventura"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "All the people that question me, I turn around and say well, how much independent investigation have you done?", "question_tokens": ["All", "the", "people", "that", "question", "me", ",", "I", "turn", "around", "and", "say", "well", ",", "how", "much", "independent", "investigation", "have", "you", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Jesse Ventura for the hour.", "answer_tokens": ["Jesse", "Ventura", "for", "the", "hour", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What have you made of it from your vantage point?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "made", "of", "it", "from", "your", "vantage", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, you probably shouldn't ask me that considering my TV show is called \"Conspiracy Theories.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "probably", "should", "n't", "ask", "me", "that", "considering", "my", "TV", "show", "is", "called", "``", "Conspiracy", "Theories", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "RP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What do they create there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "create", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, it's -- what it is, it's 50 antennas basically that put out 50,000 watts, which is the maximum you can for radio, and it combines and shoots it up into the atmosphere, and they ricochet it off back he ground.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "what", "it", "is", ",", "it", "'s", "50", "antennas", "basically", "that", "put", "out", "50,000", "watts", ",", "which", "is", "the", "maximum", "you", "can", "for", "radio", ",", "and", "it", "combines", "and", "shoots", "it", "up", "into", "the", "atmosphere", ",", "and", "they", "ricochet", "it", "off", "back", "he", "ground", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What's your take?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, my take is that we're only worried if there's a corporate interest.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "take", "is", "that", "we", "'re", "only", "worried", "if", "there", "'s", "a", "corporate", "interest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No, I see it being run by corporations, though.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "see", "it", "being", "run", "by", "corporations", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "When you see what was apparently about to happen in Benghazi in Libya where it appeared that Gadhafi was about to slaughter possibly hundreds of thousands of his own people, is there not a humanitarian duty for countries like America to try and prevent that if they can?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "was", "apparently", "about", "to", "happen", "in", "Benghazi", "in", "Libya", "where", "it", "appeared", "that", "Gadhafi", "was", "about", "to", "slaughter", "possibly", "hundreds", "of", "thousands", "of", "his", "own", "people", ",", "is", "there", "not", "a", "humanitarian", "duty", "for", "countries", "like", "America", "to", "try", "and", "prevent", "that", "if", "they", "can", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "JJR", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi", "Libya", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Oh, he was?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "he", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "But why is it always the United States?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "is", "it", "always", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Do you think America has for too long been the world's policemen?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "America", "has", "for", "too", "long", "been", "the", "world", "'s", "policemen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "We shut down all the bases overseas?", "question_tokens": ["We", "shut", "down", "all", "the", "bases", "overseas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "We can get anywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "get", "anywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "So you're saying the mere presence of American bases is inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "saying", "the", "mere", "presence", "of", "American", "bases", "is", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Why do we have bases in foreign countries?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "we", "have", "bases", "in", "foreign", "countries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, the argument is to try and prevent uprisings of the --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "argument", "is", "to", "try", "and", "prevent", "uprisings", "of", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "And is it actually perversely -- could it be helpful now that places like China are emerging ahead of us?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "actually", "perversely", "--", "could", "it", "be", "helpful", "now", "that", "places", "like", "China", "are", "emerging", "ahead", "of", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, I think it's very easy to see what's going on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "easy", "to", "see", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "You were serving, is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "serving", ",", "is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I don't -- when I got back -- I'm a Navy SEAL, when I got back from my service overseas in my first deployment, the My Lai massacre had just happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "when", "I", "got", "back", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "Navy", "SEAL", ",", "when", "I", "got", "back", "from", "my", "service", "overseas", "in", "my", "first", "deployment", ",", "the", "My", "Lai", "massacre", "had", "just", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Harvard"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Yes, I mean the point I was going to make is what lesson did you learn being in the military about the reality of war?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", "the", "point", "I", "was", "going", "to", "make", "is", "what", "lesson", "did", "you", "learn", "being", "in", "the", "military", "about", "the", "reality", "of", "war", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Probably the biggest lesson I learned happened in 2004 when I was teaching at Harvard.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "biggest", "lesson", "I", "learned", "happened", "in", "2004", "when", "I", "was", "teaching", "at", "Harvard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "I mean do you think as a matter of principle as with Vietnam, (INAUDIBLE) in Libya, that America and the West generally should stay out of civil war?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "think", "as", "a", "matter", "of", "principle", "as", "with", "Vietnam", ",", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "in", "Libya", ",", "that", "America", "and", "the", "West", "generally", "should", "stay", "out", "of", "civil", "war", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam", "Libya", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Let countries fight it out if they want to?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "countries", "fight", "it", "out", "if", "they", "want", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Could be a more sensible and dare I say a cheaper foreign policy?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "be", "a", "more", "sensible", "and", "dare", "I", "say", "a", "cheaper", "foreign", "policy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, I don't know, it would certainly be cheaper.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "it", "would", "certainly", "be", "cheaper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Does it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, the alternative is you just let every country get on with it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "alternative", "is", "you", "just", "let", "every", "country", "get", "on", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Shouldn't countries determine their own destiny?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "n't", "countries", "determine", "their", "own", "destiny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Possibly, so you end up then with the possibility of further Irans, which is dangerous to world peace.", "answer_tokens": ["Possibly", ",", "so", "you", "end", "up", "then", "with", "the", "possibility", "of", "further", "Irans", ",", "which", "is", "dangerous", "to", "world", "peace", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Well, for example, by your yardstick, if you don't go and get involved in places like Egypt, when there's an uprising as there was, and you get extremists in charge who decide they want to punish America and they want to get together with the Syrians and the Yemen -- Yemeni and the Iranians, and they're going to stop any oil coming out of the Middle East to America, then what?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "example", ",", "by", "your", "yardstick", ",", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "go", "and", "get", "involved", "in", "places", "like", "Egypt", ",", "when", "there", "'s", "an", "uprising", "as", "there", "was", ",", "and", "you", "get", "extremists", "in", "charge", "who", "decide", "they", "want", "to", "punish", "America", "and", "they", "want", "to", "get", "together", "with", "the", "Syrians", "and", "the", "Yemen", "--", "Yemeni", "and", "the", "Iranians", ",", "and", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "stop", "any", "oil", "coming", "out", "of", "the", "Middle", "East", "to", "America", ",", "then", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt", "America", "Yemen", "Middle East", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Do you want to know why we're in Afghanistan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "know", "why", "we", "'re", "in", "Afghanistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I'm fascinated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "fascinated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 212, "question": "So why don't they just, Piers, tell me the truth?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "do", "n't", "they", "just", ",", "Piers", ",", "tell", "me", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "But Jesse, that's not --", "answer_tokens": ["But", "Jesse", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama", "Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What did he risk it for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "risk", "it", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "He risked it because everybody knows Osama bin Laden was training people to commit atrocities in Afghanistan.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "risked", "it", "because", "everybody", "knows", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "was", "training", "people", "to", "commit", "atrocities", "in", "Afghanistan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "We all know that?", "question_tokens": ["We", "all", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "That's a fact.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "fact", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "How come -- Piers, how come 2,000 architects and engineers met in San Francisco demanding a new investigation?", "question_tokens": ["How", "come", "--", "Piers", ",", "how", "come", "2,000", "architects", "and", "engineers", "met", "in", "San", "Francisco", "demanding", "a", "new", "investigation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", ":", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Jesse, you're the first guest I've had where we're still arguing in the breaks.", "answer_tokens": ["Jesse", ",", "you", "'re", "the", "first", "guest", "I", "'ve", "had", "where", "we", "'re", "still", "arguing", "in", "the", "breaks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["San Francisco"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "PERSON": ["William Harvey"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Who did that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "It was done by William Harvey, who was the head of the CIA's assassination unit at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "done", "by", "William", "Harvey", ",", "who", "was", "the", "head", "of", "the", "CIA", "'s", "assassination", "unit", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Doesn't mean anything, does it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "mean", "anything", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I can be slightly naive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "be", "slightly", "naive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Because I tried them and I'm an expert marksman, he wasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "tried", "them", "and", "I", "'m", "an", "expert", "marksman", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Did Neil Armstrong land on the moon?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Neil", "Armstrong", "land", "on", "the", "moon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Neil Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Yes, I think he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Why would you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Because we have the technology to get there.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "have", "the", "technology", "to", "get", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 318, "question": "What type of investigation is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "type", "of", "investigation", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I have never, ever heard anybody suggest the investigations were closed on the Monday within hours --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "never", ",", "ever", "heard", "anybody", "suggest", "the", "investigations", "were", "closed", "on", "the", "Monday", "within", "hours", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Well, do you believe everything you read in the papers?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "everything", "you", "read", "in", "the", "papers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I did -- I did then.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "--", "I", "did", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["John Kennedy"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "-- in your mother's newspaper from the time?", "question_tokens": ["--", "in", "your", "mother", "'s", "newspaper", "from", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I've studied John Kennedy for 25 years, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "studied", "John", "Kennedy", "for", "25", "years", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Your theory of 9/11 is what?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "theory", "of", "9/11", "is", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "My theory of 9/11 is that we certainly -- at the best we knew it was going to happen.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "theory", "of", "9/11", "is", "that", "we", "certainly", "--", "at", "the", "best", "we", "knew", "it", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August 6th"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Are you suggesting he knew?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "suggesting", "he", "knew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "If you look -- well, put it to you this way, the August 6th memo was pretty clear.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "look", "--", "well", ",", "put", "it", "to", "you", "this", "way", ",", "the", "August", "6th", "memo", "was", "pretty", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Are you -- do you genuinely believe, Jesse Ventura, that President George W. Bush knew 9/11 was going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "do", "you", "genuinely", "believe", ",", "Jesse", "Ventura", ",", "that", "President", "George", "W.", "Bush", "knew", "9/11", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Ventura", "George W. Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Why do you say it then?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "say", "it", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Well, why do you say it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "why", "do", "you", "say", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "But I believe Dick Cheney knew it.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "believe", "Dick", "Cheney", "knew", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"], "PERSON": ["John Ashcroft"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "You believe he knew it was going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "believe", "he", "knew", "it", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "ENTURA: I believe they had -- well, why did John Ashcroft quit flying commercial planes that summer and switch only to private planes.", "answer_tokens": ["ENTURA", ":", "I", "believe", "they", "had", "--", "well", ",", "why", "did", "John", "Ashcroft", "quit", "flying", "commercial", "planes", "that", "summer", "and", "switch", "only", "to", "private", "planes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Homeland Security"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Unfortunately they exposed a massive flaw Homeland Security.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", "they", "exposed", "a", "massive", "flaw", "Homeland", "Security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Then what was it?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "what", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "They floor was that these guys have been trailing and often aiming to go one way, aiming to land planes in a certain manner.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "floor", "was", "that", "these", "guys", "have", "been", "trailing", "and", "often", "aiming", "to", "go", "one", "way", ",", "aiming", "to", "land", "planes", "in", "a", "certain", "manner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "I mean do you believe Princess Diana was murdered?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "believe", "Princess", "Diana", "was", "murdered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "No, I don't look that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "look", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "But what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You don't believe that when two large planes hit the World Trade Center, hit both towers and they explode that that couldn't bring down two buildings?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "when", "two", "large", "planes", "hit", "the", "World", "Trade", "Center", ",", "hit", "both", "towers", "and", "they", "explode", "that", "that", "could", "n't", "bring", "down", "two", "buildings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Now if everything took place, Piers, 150 floors up, why was there molten metal underneath?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "if", "everything", "took", "place", ",", "Piers", ",", "150", "floors", "up", ",", "why", "was", "there", "molten", "metal", "underneath", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "You wrote --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "wrote", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States Navy"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "You consider yourself to be a good American?", "question_tokens": ["You", "consider", "yourself", "to", "be", "a", "good", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I've been a mayor, I've been a governor, and I served six years and was honorably discharged from the United States Navy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "a", "mayor", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "a", "governor", ",", "and", "I", "served", "six", "years", "and", "was", "honorably", "discharged", "from", "the", "United", "States", "Navy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Do you believe it happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "it", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "So he didn't know?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "did", "n't", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Did he know or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "know", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you agree with Ron Paul there?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "Ron", "Paul", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Wikileaks couldn't?", "question_tokens": ["Wikileaks", "could", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Once the mission is over, we're not jeopardizing --", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "the", "mission", "is", "over", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "jeopardizing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "You don't think anything published in Wikileaks could possibly jeopardize lives or military operations?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "anything", "published", "in", "Wikileaks", "could", "possibly", "jeopardize", "lives", "or", "military", "operations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Let's go to this young man that's in prison right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "go", "to", "this", "young", "man", "that", "'s", "in", "prison", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wikileaks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 534, "question": "So what do we get to know about?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "do", "we", "get", "to", "know", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "But my point --", "answer_tokens": ["But", "my", "point", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Did you believe it was in the public interest that Wikileaks reveal, for example, that Colonel Gadhafi had four mistresses?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "believe", "it", "was", "in", "the", "public", "interest", "that", "Wikileaks", "reveal", ",", "for", "example", ",", "that", "Colonel", "Gadhafi", "had", "four", "mistresses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I could care less how many women Colonel Gadhafi has.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "care", "less", "how", "many", "women", "Colonel", "Gadhafi", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "But is it in the public interest to reveal that information?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "in", "the", "public", "interest", "to", "reveal", "that", "information", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "They did about your son, right?", "question_tokens": ["They", "did", "about", "your", "son", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "They trumped up charges.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "trumped", "up", "charges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "OK, then why is it OK for our -- why is it OK for them to expose my private stuff?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "then", "why", "is", "it", "OK", "for", "our", "--", "why", "is", "it", "OK", "for", "them", "to", "expose", "my", "private", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I'm not saying it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Shouldn't they be the ones who have put America in danger, the ones who wrote it?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "n't", "they", "be", "the", "ones", "who", "have", "put", "America", "in", "danger", ",", "the", "ones", "who", "wrote", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "JJR", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "No, because the whole point of being a diplomat is that when you report to your government, around the world -- wait, wait, let me finish.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "the", "whole", "point", "of", "being", "a", "diplomat", "is", "that", "when", "you", "report", "to", "your", "government", ",", "around", "the", "world", "--", "wait", ",", "wait", ",", "let", "me", "finish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Would you agree if the CIA discovered tomorrow that they knew where Osama bin Laden was, that he should be assassinated?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "if", "the", "CIA", "discovered", "tomorrow", "that", "they", "knew", "where", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "was", ",", "that", "he", "should", "be", "assassinated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What about Gadhafi?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Gadhafi", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "You don't care?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Jesse, with respect, isn't that exactly what Navy SEALS do all the time?", "question_tokens": ["Jesse", ",", "with", "respect", ",", "is", "n't", "that", "exactly", "what", "Navy", "SEALS", "do", "all", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "ENTURA: No.", "answer_tokens": ["ENTURA", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"], "PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Kind of like Curveball?", "question_tokens": ["Kind", "of", "like", "Curveball", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Wait, wait.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", ",", "wait", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "How do you get it out of them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "it", "out", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "You just have to do what you can to attempt to get it out of them, but torture is not the answer.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "just", "have", "to", "do", "what", "you", "can", "to", "attempt", "to", "get", "it", "out", "of", "them", ",", "but", "torture", "is", "not", "the", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "So you think it's inconsistent?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "inconsistent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "ENTURA: I think it's very inconsistent.", "answer_tokens": ["ENTURA", ":", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "inconsistent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo Bay"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Why weren't they water boarded to find out what they knew?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "n't", "they", "water", "boarded", "to", "find", "out", "what", "they", "knew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "What do you think of Guantanamo Bay --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Guantanamo", "Bay", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Why were these guys water boarded and these guys not water boarded?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "these", "guys", "water", "boarded", "and", "these", "guys", "not", "water", "boarded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Yes, but remember the dynamic of the interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "remember", "the", "dynamic", "of", "the", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "What did you think of Guantanamo Bay?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "Guantanamo", "Bay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "I think it's atrocious.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "atrocious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo Bay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Your style is different than mine.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "style", "is", "different", "than", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Entertainment?", "question_tokens": ["Entertainment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "It's dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "You let this guy spout off that President Obama is a member of the CIA.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "let", "this", "guy", "spout", "off", "that", "President", "Obama", "is", "a", "member", "of", "the", "CIA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP"], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Can you say he's not?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "say", "he", "'s", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yes!", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Just call it a gut feeling, Jesse.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "call", "it", "a", "gut", "feeling", ",", "Jesse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "What do you object to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "object", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "I object to the fact that I have metal in my body.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "object", "to", "the", "fact", "that", "I", "have", "metal", "in", "my", "body", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Should nobody be searched?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "nobody", "be", "searched", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "No, I'm saying only me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "saying", "only", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Who would you search?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "search", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "No, you asked me about my court case.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "asked", "me", "about", "my", "court", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Why just you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "just", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Because of who I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "of", "who", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "You believe in profiling, basically?", "question_tokens": ["You", "believe", "in", "profiling", ",", "basically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Would you only profile Muslims at airports?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "only", "profile", "Muslims", "at", "airports", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Because you're worried about being inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'re", "worried", "about", "being", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "You cannot insult me into thinking you're going to get something out of me by calling me a coward.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "not", "insult", "me", "into", "thinking", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "something", "out", "of", "me", "by", "calling", "me", "a", "coward", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Have they caught anyone?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "caught", "anyone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Clarify.", "answer_tokens": ["Clarify", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "For?", "question_tokens": ["For", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "With what they're doing at the airports.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "at", "the", "airports", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "How stupid would that be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "stupid", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "Most terrorists do the same thing again and again.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "terrorists", "do", "the", "same", "thing", "again", "and", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "No, you know why we picked 63?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "know", "why", "we", "picked", "63", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Well, because I don't believe the power structure would allow a rogue like me to get in there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "the", "power", "structure", "would", "allow", "a", "rogue", "like", "me", "to", "get", "in", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "What are the other barriers to you being president, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "other", "barriers", "to", "you", "being", "president", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "The fact that I -- well, I hate the fund-raising.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "fact", "that", "I", "--", "well", ",", "I", "hate", "the", "fund-raising", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "EX", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "What about religion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "religion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "Well, I have a problem there too, because I've now admitted I'm an atheist.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "a", "problem", "there", "too", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "now", "admitted", "I", "'m", "an", "atheist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "Are you going to stay with Jesse Ventura?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "stay", "with", "Jesse", "Ventura", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "No, I'll kill him.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ll", "kill", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Ventura"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "When?", "question_tokens": ["When", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "I don't know yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "Soon?", "question_tokens": ["Soon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "But the day's coming.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "the", "day", "'s", "coming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "So the death of Jesse comes in a year?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "death", "of", "Jesse", "comes", "in", "a", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "Possibly.", "answer_tokens": ["Possibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "Gone?", "question_tokens": ["Gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Gone.", "answer_tokens": ["Gone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "All over?", "question_tokens": ["All", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "All over.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110404pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Do you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "was", "a", "mistake", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "Paula", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "Certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]